Shocking. Depraved. Sickening. And they're only Kids.
Kids is a drama, crime film directed by Larry Clark.
A day in the life of a group of teens as they travel around New York
City skating, drinking, smoking and deflowering virgins.
Telly, played by Leo Fitzpatrick.
Casper, played by Justin Pierce.
Jennie, played by Chloë Sevigny.
Ruby, played by Rosario Dawson.
Darcy, played by Yakira Peguero.
Misha, played by Atabey Rodriguez.
Kids is a 1995 American independent coming-of-age drama film directed by Larry Clark and written
by Harmony Korine in their directorial and screenwriting debuts, respectively.
It stars Leo Fitzpatrick, Justin Pierce and Chloë Sevigny in their film debuts.
Fitzpatrick, Pierce, Sevigny, and other newcomers including Rosario
Dawson portray a group of teenagers in New York City.
They are characterized as libertines, who engage in sexual acts and
recreational substance abuse, over the course of a single day.
Ben Detrick of the New York Times has described the film as "Lord of
the Flies with skateboards, nitrous oxide and hip-hop...
There is no thunderous moral reckoning, only observational detachment." The film caused
controversy upon its release in 1995 over its treatment of the subject matter.
It received an NC-17 rating from the MPAA, but was released without a rating.
Critical response was mixed, and the film grossed
$20.4 million on a $1.5 million budget.
It is now considered a cult classic.
The film explores themes of puberty, first time, new
york city, drug abuse, coming of age.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.